Leonard Carmichael Papers ca.1917-1973 Mss.B.C212
American Philosophical Society
- Leonard Carmichael Papers, ca. 1917-1973 (Box 1)
  - Tufts Univ. - Various Funds, Scholarships, etc.
    - Wren, Paul I
    - Houston, Clarence P
    - Miller, George S
    - Averill, Harvey E
    - Davidson, Sidney W
    - Kajander, John
  - Tufts Univ. - Washington Tufts Club
    - Ackerman, Robert
    - Peterson, Austin G
    - Wessell, Nils Y
    - Nelson, William H
    - Morton, J W
  - Tufts Univ. - Weekly - General
  - Tufts Univ. - Wessell, Nils Y, President
    - Marshall, Laurence K
    - Roeder, Kenneth D
    - Averill, H E
    - Hill, Robert W
    - Bush, Vannevar
    - Jones, Herbert M
    - Hershey, Lewis B
    - Carbone, Gaetano A
    - Jackson, Richard
    - Smith, H P
    - Gates, Thomas S, Jr.
    - Friend, Victor A
    - Tilton, John P
    - Anderson, Arthur J
    - Gregg, David
    - Blotner, Harry
  - Tufts Weekly Articles
  - Tukey, John Wilder
    - Martin, William McChesney, Jr.
  - Tulane Univ. - Board of Visitors
    - Longenecker, Herbert E
    - Scheps, Clarence
    - Morris, Joseph C
    - Riopelle, Arthur J
    - Fenner, Darwin S
    - Field, Beatrice M
  - Tulane University - Board of Visitors Annual Meeting
    - Morris, Joseph C
    - Generes, A P
  - Tulane Univ. Delta Regional Primate Center
    - Riopelle, Arthur J
    - Bowery, Thomas G
    - Longenecker, Herbert E
    - Sperry, Roger W
    - Thompson, Clare W
    - Dorst, Jean
    - Jones, Clyde
    - Snider, Edwin W
    - Feith, Edward F
    - Nauta, Walle J H
    - Bang, Frederik B
    - Stewart, T D
    - Geldard, Frank A
    - Wetzel, Albert J
    - Walsh, John J
    - Besch, Everett D
    - Mason, R P
    - Fraga, Antonio M
    - Hofer, Helmut O
    - Marler, Peter
  - Tulane Univ. - Delta Regional Primate Research Center -- Riopelle, Arthur J., Hofer, H O
    - Morris, Joseph C
    - Longenecker, Herbert E
  - Tulane University - General Correspondence
    - Morris, Joseph C
    - Fenner, Darwin S
    - Jones, Joseph Merrick
    - Guillory, Barbara Marie
    - Lumiansky, R M
    - Elloie, Mrs. Pearlie Hardin
    - Sterling, J E Wallace
    - Longenecker, Herbert Eugene
    - Stanton, Frank
    - Smith, Howard K
    - Lapham, M E
    - Lyons, Alvin L
    - Stibbs, John H
    - Harris, Rufus C
    - Wooton, Paul
    - Ault, W L
    - Renegar, Horace
  - Tulane Univ. - Publications, Reports, Etc.
    - Morris, Joseph C
  - Tulane Univ. - St. Denis J. Villere and Co. Reports
    - Generes, A P
    - Jones, Joseph Merrick
  - Turkel, Henry
  - Turkey
    - McKnew, Thomas W
    - Mardin, Yusuf Sitki
    - Esenbel, Melih
  - Turner, George T
  - Turner, Harold M
  - Turner, William D
  - Tutelian, Stephen
  - Tuve, Merle A
  - Twentieth Century Ass'n.
    - Reed, Grace P
  - Twitmyer, Edwin B
  - Two Thousand Men of Achievement
  - Tyler, H T
  - Tyroler, Charles, II
  - Tyle Review
  - Udahl, Lee
    - Harner, Michael J
    - Lowry, MacNeil
  - Uhl, W L
  - Uhlaner, Julius E
  - Uhrbrock, Richard S
  - Ullman, A
  - Ullman, Roy R
  - Ulus, Erdogan
  - Unconventional Material
  - Underhill, A Heaton
  - Underhill, O E
  - Undersea Warfare (Committee on)
  - Underwood, Benton J
  - Underwood Corp.
  - UNESCO
  - UNESCO - Braverman, A Marvin
    - Minnich, L Arthur
    - Laves, Walter H C
    - Jennings, Coleman A
    - Bluestein, Jerome N
    - Fobes, John E
  - UNESCO - U.S. National Meeting, Oct. 14-16, 1954
    - McCullough, Max
    - Alexander, Mrs. Stewart
  - UNESCO - U.S. National Meeting, Nov. 2-3, 1955
    - McCullough, Max
  - UNESCO - U.S. National Meeting, Sept. 17-18, 1956
  - UNESCO - U.S. National Meeting, Nov. 5-6, 1957
  - Union College
  - Union College Character Research Project
  - United Arab Republic
  - United Kingdom Scientific Mission
  - United Kingdom Scientific Museum
  - United Negro College Fund
  - U.S. Army Scientific Advisory Panel
  - U.S. Capitol Historycal Society
  - U.S. Civil Service Commission
  - U.S. Civil Service Commission. Qualification Code
  - U.S. Coast and Geodetic Survey
    - Jones, Don A
  - U.S. Committee for National Morale. Age Conflicts and Radical Youth
  - U.S. Committee for National Morale. Bibliography
  - U.S. Committee for National Morale. Cultural anthoropology and morale
  - U.S. Committee for National Morale. Definition of Morale
    - Dept. of Documentation and Bibliography.
    - Draft of principles governing a national morale service
    - European "Fifth Column" and American morale - resistance
    - Family morale
    - Fascism and Italian morale
    - Foreign language broadcasts of domestic origin
    - German devices for building industrial morale
    - Industrial morale: basic concepts
    - Memorandum concerning an American morale service abroad
    - Memorandum on problems of military morale in the U.S.combat forces
    - Morale implication of child development
    - Morale in China
    - Morale in Germany
    - Morale in Hungary
    - Morale in Spain
    - National Morale
    - Organization at work
    - Outline of an industrial service
    - Plan for a national morale service
    - Plan for measuring industrial morale
    - Proposal to establish a syndicate to supply foreign language publications and for the defense against subversive propaganda
  - U.S. Committee for National Morale. Psychology in the service of morale
  - U.S. Committee for National Morale. Radio intelligence and problems of morale
    - Role of a bibliographer in a morale service
    - Role of a psychiatrist in a morale service
    - Scientific techniques for measuring morale
    - Survey of personal practices in the U.S.
  - U.S. Committee on national honors
  - U.S. Department of Agriculture
  - U.S. Department of Commerca
  - U.S. Department of Transportation
  - U.S. Exposition of Science and Industry, Inc.
  - U.S. Flag Foundation, Inc.
  - U.S. GPO Style Manual
  - U.S.-Japan cooperative science program planning meeting on Primate Biology
  - U.S. Military Academy
  - U.S. Military Academy - Board of Visitors
  - U.S. Mint
  - U.S. National Commission for UNESCO
  - U.S. Naval Academy
  - U.S. Naval Medical Research Laboratory
  - U.S. Naval Observatory
  - U.S. Naval Research - General
  - U.S. Naval Research Advistory Committee
  - U.S. Naval Research Advistory Committee. Basic Research
  - U.S. Naval Research, London Office
  - U.S. Navy Training Device Center
  - U.S. Navy Contract with the Smithsonian
  - U.S. Navy Contracts - Letters to Consultants
  - U.S. Navy Material Command
  - U.S. Navy Secretary of the Navy's Advisory board of scientific education
  - U.S. News and World Report
  - U.S. Order of Washington
  - U.S. Selective Service Commission
  - U.S. State Department. Special fine arts committee
  - U.S. Trade Mark Association
  - Universalist Historical Society
  - Universitas
  - University Clib of Boston
  - University Club of New York
  - University of California Medical Center
  - University of Chicago - Dept. of Bacteriology and Parasitology
  - University of Chicago
    - White, Leonard D
    - Hutchinson, William T
    - Marenberg, Philip P
    - Hess, Robert D
    - Taliaferro, W H
    - Hutchins, Robert M
  - University of Chicago Press
    - Morin, Alexander J
    - Veith, Ilza
    - Taliaferro, W H
    - Harrison, Carter
  - University of Chicago - Publications in Biology and Medicine
  - University of Houston
  - University of Kentucky
  - University of Kentucky Press
  - University of Minnesota - Bulletin
  - University of Pennsylvania
  - University of Rochester
  - University of Rochester - Academic appointment.
  - University of Rochester - Inauguration of Wallis
  - University of Southern California - School of Education
  - University of Southern California - Psycology
  - University of Vermont
  - University Research Associates
  - Unknown
  - Unofficial Ambassadors, Inc.
  - Upton, Charles M
  - Upton, Ernest W
  - Upton, Morgan
  - Urban geography
  - Urdal, Mrs. Arthur
  - Urquhart, Helen Lowe
  - Usen, Irving
  - Ushiba, Nobuhiko
  - Utt, James B. "The Government and Fine Arts."
  - Vacation - New England's Vacation Business
  - Vail, Guy W
  - Valente, Mozart Gurgel, Jr.
  - Valentine
  - Valentine, Alan
  - Valentine, Mrs. Alan
  - Valentine, Willard L
  - Vamvaketis, Mrs. Stephen
  - Van Allen, James
  - Van Auken, Mrs. Cecelia
  - Van Cott, Harold P
  - Van Cure, Charles
  - Van der Haagen, J K
  - Vander Poel, Halsted
  - Van de Woestyne, Royal S
  - Van der Walter, Marjorie
  - Van Gelder, Richard G
  - Van Meter, Ralph
  - Van Nice, Robert L
  - Van Norman, Mabel
  - Van Nostrand Company, Inc.
  - Vance, Jeanne K
  - Vance, Thomas F
  - Van Patten, Cornelius C
  - Van Pelt, Alexander
  - Van Wagenen, W P
  - Van Wart, Mrs. Edwin Clark
  - Vassar College
  - Vaughan, Wayland F
  - Venice, Aid to
  - Vera, Alice I
  - Vernon, Jack A
  - Verplanck, William S
  - Versen, Kurt
  - Verworn, Max
  - Veterans Administration
    - General
    - Insurance
  - Vocational rehabilitation
  - Viaud, Gaston
  - Victory, John F
  - Vienna, University of
  - Viets, Henry R
  - Villesbrunne, Gerard de la
  - Vinacke, W Edgar
  - Viner, Jeanne S
  - Virgin, Mrs. Edward
  - Vision
    - Vision - Acuity
    - Vision - Binocular
    - Vision - Color
    - Vision - Cortex
    - Vision - Eye
    - Vision - Eye motor mechanism
    - Vision - Luminosity
    - Vision - Lectures
  - Visitors and telephone calls
  - Visual fatigue
    - Visual fatigue - Apparatus
    - Visual fatigue - Chapters and appendix
    - Visual fatigue - Comprehensive check
    - Visual fatigue - Copyright lists
    - Visual fatigue - Correspondence
    - Visual fatigue - Data
    - Visual fatigue - Draft
    - Visual fatigue - Finances
    - Visual fatigue - Graphs
    - Visual fatigue - Miscellaneous
    - Visual fatigue - Permissions to reproduce
    - Visual fatigue - Preface
    - Visual fatigue - Questionnaire
    - Visual fatigue - Trial sheets
  - Visual Research, Institute of
  - Visual fatigue study
  - Vitae of various individuals
  - Vitales, Morris S
  - Vocational bureaus
  - Voeks, Virginia
  - Voet, Leon
  - Vogt, Herbert J
  - Volkmann, John
  - Vom Rath, Mrs. Cecilia
  - Von Berthold, Karl Hemrick
  - Von Bracken, H
  - Von Braun, Wernher
  - Von Selzam, Mrs. Edward C
  - Voorhis, Harold O
  - Vora, C H
  - Vorys, John M
  - Vosburgh, Mrs. Pat
  - Wachenheimer, Mrs. Therese F
  - Wadsworth, Julius
  - Wages in New England
  - Wagman, Jules L
  - Wagner, Joseph F
  - Wagner, Kip
  - Wagner, Ralph E
  - Wagner, Thomas Rowan
  - Wagoner, Kenneth S
  - Wagoner, Lovisa C
  - Wainwright, Don
  - Wait, J S
  - Wakelin, James H, Jr.
  - Walk, Richard D
  - Walker, Egbert H
  - Walker, Eric A
  - Walker, Ernest P
  - Walker, John
  - Walker, John S
  - Walker, Paul H
  - Walker, R E
  - Walkley, Mrs. Raymond L
  - Wall, Alexander J
  - Wallace, De Witt
  - Wallace, Robert F
  - Wallace, S Rains
  - Wallace, William
  - Wallen, I E
  - Waller, Theodore
  - Walsh, Mrs. B Timothy
  - Walsh, Jeffery J
  - Walshe, F M R
  - Walter, Alice A
  - Walter, Mrs. Howland
  - Walter Reed Army Medical Center
  - Walters, Mrs. Arthur
  - Walton, Henry A
  - Walton Smith, F G
  - Wands, Mrs. Burton
  - Wang, Ging-Hsi
  - Wang, Yvonne J
  - Waples, Douglas
  - War Ration Stamp Books
  - Ward, Roswell
  - Ward Howell Associates
  - Warden, C J
  - Ware, Leonard
  - Warkentin, John
  - Warner, Caleb
  - Warner, Frederick L
  - Warner, Lucien H
  - Warner Brothers Pictures, Inc.
  - Warren, Mrs. Catherine C
  - Warren, Earl
  - Warren, Howard Crosby, 6 folders
    - Warren, Howard Crosby, 2 folders
    - Warren, Howard Crosby. Dictionary of psychology, 2 folders
    - Warren, Howard Crosby. Medal, 2 folders
  - Warren, Mrs. Hugh
  - Warren, Howard C
  - Warren, J M
  - Warren, Neil D
  - Warren, W P
  - Washburn, Arthur L
  - Washburn, Bradford
  - Washburn, Charles W
  - Washburn, Margaret Floy
  - Washburn, Ruth W
  - Washburn, S L
  - Washburn, Wilcomb E
  - Washburne, John N
  - Washburne, Norman F
  - Washington Academy of Sciences
  - Washington Board of Trade
  - Washington Cathedral, 33 folders
    - Building Committee, 12 folders
    - Cathedral Chapter, 7 folders
    - Executive committee
    - Finance committee, 2 folders
    - Fund drive, 8 folders
    - General, 3 folders
  - Washington College
  - Washington (D.C.) School of Psychiatry
  - Washington Daily News
  - Washington housing
  - Washington History of Science Club
  - Washington Institute of Foreign Affairs
  - Washington Post
  - Washington Post - Book Reviews
  - Washington Public Opinion Laboratory
  - Washington State Historical Society
  - Wasley, William W
  - Watch repairs, etc.
  - Water, Marjorie van de
  - Waterman, Alan T
  - Waterman, Talbot Howe
  - Waters, Edward N
  - Waters, R H
  - Watkins, C Malcolm
  - Watkins, Elmore
  - Watkins, M S
  - Watson, Arthur E
  - Watson, Goodwin
  - Watson, J B
  - Watson, Norman S
  - Watson, Robert I
  - Watson, Thomas J
  - Watts, Mrs. Carolyn Troy
  - Watts, Charles H
  - Wayland-Smith, Mrs. Prudence
  - Wayne State University
  - Weatherman, Larry
  - Weaver, E G
  - Weaver, Frederic N
  - Weaver, Rufus B
  - Weaver, Warren
  - Webb, James Edwin
  - Webb, Robert W
  - Weber, C O
  - Wechsler, David
  - Wedel, Waldo R
  - Wedin, Bertil
  - Weeks, Sinclair
  - Weerasinghe, Oliver
  - Weiant, Elizabeth A
  - Weigel,John C
  - Weigle, Richard D
  - Weinstein, Eugene A
  - Weiss, Albert P
  - Weiss, Mrs. Elsie Z
  - Weiss, Helena
  - Weiss, Paul
  - Weiss, Philip
  - Welch, Arnold D
  - Welch, Austin H
  - Welch, Bruce
  - Welch, Edward C
  - Welch, Emily
  - Welch, W.M., Scientific Company
  - Weld, Harry P
  - Weld, W E
  - Weldin, John C
  - Wellesley Club of Boston
  - Wellesley College
  - Wellington, G R
  - Wellman, Bertram
  - Wells, F L
  - Welsh, Peter C
  - Wendt, G R
  - Wendt, Richard
  - Wengenroth, Stow
  - Wenk, Edward, Jr.
  - Wenley, Archibald Gibson
  - Wentzel, Volkmar Kurt
  - Wermiel, Stephen
  - Werner, Bruno E
  - Werner, Heinz
  - Werner, Thomas
  - Wertheimer, Max
  - Wescott, G W
  - Wesleyan University Press
  - Wessell, N J
  - Wessell, Nils Y
  - West, Andrew Fleming
  - West, Christine
  - West, Millard F, Jr.
  - West, Thomas H, Jr.
  - West Indies Students Liaison Office
  - Western Psychological Services
  - Western Reserve University
  - Western Union International, Inc.
  - Westfall, L C
  - Westinghouse Broadcasting Company
  - Westinghouse Calendar
  - Westinghouse Calendars, published by Houghton Mifflin Company
  - Westinghouse-Safety System at Carmichael Home
  - Westinghouse - Selections Committee for the Time Capsule Contents
  - Westrate, J Lee
  - WETA - Channel 26
  - Wetmore, Alexander
  - Wetter, Allen H
  - Wever, Ernest Glen
  - Wheeler, Mrs. Alexander
  - Wheeler, Catherine
  - Wheeler, Mrs. Colin L
  - Wheeler, Frances E
  - Wheeler, John Archibald
  - Wheeler, [Mary C.] School
  - Wheeler, Raymond H
  - Wheeler, T Ames
  - Wheeler, W M
  - Wheeler School
  - Whipple, Fred L
  - Whipple, George H
  - Whipple, Mary A
  - Whitaker, Elizabeth
  - White, Charles H
  - White, Mrs. Francis P
  - White, Goodrich C
  - White, Harold L
  - White, J Mattocks
  - White, John
  - White, Mrs. Laura
  - White, Lawrence Grant
  - White, Lynn, Jr.
  - White, Paul Dudley
  - White, Sally
  - White, W J
  - White, Wendell
  - White, William C
  - White, William J
  - White House Conference on Children and Youth
  - White House Conference on International Cooperation
  - White House Historical Association
  - White House Historical Association. Board of Directors
  - White Oak Psychological Center
  - Whitehill, Mrs. Walter Muir
  - Whitelaw, Robert N S
  - Whitely, Paul L
  - Whitmore, Frank C, Jr.
  - Whitney, Frederick D
  - Whitney, Thomas H P
  - Whittemore, Irving C
  - Whittemore, Laurence F
  - Whittier Newsletter
  - Whittingham, David K
  - Wholey, Cornelius C
  - Who's Who
  - Wicker, Fred
  - Widener, H W
  - Wiener, Margaret
  - Wiesner, Jerome B
  - Wiggam, Albert E
  - Wiggin, Sidney Cushing
  - Wigglesworth, Mrs. Richard B
  - Wilber, Charles G
  - Wildfowl Trust
  - Wiley, Alexander
  - Wiley, John, and Sons, Publishers
  - Wiley, John, and Sons, Inc.
  - Wiley, L E Sons, Publishers
  - Wilford, E Burke
  - Wilhelm, Eugene B
  - Wilinsky, Charles F
  - Wilkes, John B
  - Wilkins, Raymond S
  - Wilkinson, Robert T
  - Willey, Richard R
  - William Jewell College
  - William Volker Fund
  - Williams, Daniel G
  - Williams, Earle H
  - Williams, Floretta
  - Williams, Griffith W
  - Williams, Harry
  - Williams, Huntington
  - Williams, Lowell Winfield
  - Williams, Ralph L
  - Williams, Robert J
  - Williams, Robert R
  - Williams, Stanley B
  - Williams, Tom A
  - Williams College
  - Williamson, Mildred E
  - Willis and Sons
  - Willis, I L
  - Willis, Mrs. John T
  - Willits, Joseph H
  - Willoughby, Raymond R
  - Wilmer, Richard H
  - Wilson, Carroll L
  - Wilson, Edwin B
  - Wilson, Elizabeth
  - Wilson, Evan M
  - Wilson, Evan M, Jr.
  - Wilson, H R
  - Wilson, Howard E
  - Wilson, J Walter
  - Wilson, James Arnold
  - Wilson, John T
  - Wilson, Joseph C
  - Wilson, Orme
  - Wilson, Stephen Olin
  - Wilson, Val H
  - Wilson, Vincent, Jr.
  - Wilson, William R
  - Winchell, Florence
  - Windle, William F
  - Windsor, Alice F
  - Wine, Louis
  - Wingert, Mrs. Helen
  - Wining, Clarence H, Jr.
  - Winkler, Frederick E
  - Winn, Ira J
  - Winn, Ralph B
  - Winslow, Guy M
  - Winsor, Frederick, Jr.
  - Winslow, Graham
  - Winsor School
  - Winston, Alexander
  - Winston, Harry
  - Winston, Miriam M
  - Winston, Patrick H
  - Winterthur Museum
  - Wiren, John R
  - Wires, E Stanley
  - Wirth, Oscar
  - Wisdom
  - Wise, Watson W
  - Wispe, Lauren G
  - Withall, John G
  - Witmer School
  - Witner, Lightner
  - Wittmer, Mrs. George, III
  - Wohlfarth, William C, Jr.
  - Wolf, Gregory B
  - Wolf, Mrs. Theta Holmes
  - Wolfe, John B
  - Wolfle, Dael L
  - Wolfle, Helen L
  - Wolgast, J M
  - Wolman, Benjamin B
  - Wood, Alfred
  - Wood, Austin B
  - Wood, G F
  - Wood, H Curtis, Jr.
  - Wood, Morris Wistar
  - Wood, Theodore
  - Wood, Walter A
  - Woodcock, Herbert A
  - Woodrow, Herbert
  - Woodrow Wilson National Fellowship Foundation
  - Woodruff, John M
  - Woodruff, W
  - Woods, Loren P
  - Woods Hole Oceanographic Institution
  - Woodward and Lothrop
  - Woodworth, Lynn F
  - Woodworth, Robert S
  - Wooster, Harold
  - Wooton, Flaud
  - Wooton, Paul
  - Worcester College Club
  - Worcester Evening Gazette
  - Work Orders - Smithsonian Institution
  - Works, George A
  - World Book Company
  - World Craft Exhibit
  - World Health Organization. Yale Reference Serum Bank
  - World's Fair (Canada), 1967
  - Worm Runner's Digest
  - Worthington, Chesley
  - Wrather, Mrs. William
  - Wren, Frank G
  - Wren, Paul I
  - Wrenn, C Gilbert
  - Wrenn, Robert L
  - Wriggins, Howard
  - Wright, Donald P
  - Wright,Edith
  - Wright, Frances
  - Wright, Mrs. Frederick E
  - Wright, Howard H
  - Wright, Isaac Miles
  - Wright, J Eliot, Jr.
  - Wright, Jerauld
  - Wright, Louis B
  - Wright, Theodore P
  - Wright Memorial Dinner
  - Wrightsman, Charles B
  - Wriston, Henry M
  - Wroth, Lawrence C
  - Wu, Chen Fu
  - Wulfeck, Joseph W
  - Wullschleger, A E
  - Wulsin, F R
  - Wulsin, Mrs. Guyneth
  - Wulsin, Lucien
  - Wunsch, William
  - Wyatt, William F
  - Wyeth, Andrew
  - Wyeth, Nathan
  - Wyndham, C H
  - Wyner, Edward N
  - Wyzanski, Charles E, Jr.
  - Xerox College Publishing
  - Yacorzynski, G K
  - Yale Journal of Biology and Medicine
  - Yale University
  - Yale University Press
  - Yang, Hsi-mei
  - Yarnell, Stanley R
  - Yates, S Blake
  - Yee, Chiang
  - Yellow Springs Instrument Company
  - Yellowstone Center for Environmental Studies
  - Yerkes, David Norton
  - Yerkes, Robert M
  - Yerkes, Mrs. Robert M [Ada W.]
  - Yerkes Laboratories of Primate Biology, Inc. _____ and other institutions
    - Annotations
    - Annual Meetings
    - Annual Meetings Correspondence
    - Annual Reports
    - Board of scientific advisors
    - Bourne, Geoffrey H
    - Emory University
    - Meetings
    - Memorial statement for Mrs. Ada W. Yerkes
    - New Director
    - Newsletters
    - Nissen, Henry W
    - Possible change of location
    - Pribram, Karl H
    - Publications
    - Report
    - Riopelle, Arthur J
    - Search for a new director
    - Scientific Directors Board
    - Meetings in Atlanta
  - Yerkes Regional Primate Center
  - Yeshiva University
  - Yohner, Art, Jr.
  - York University
  - Yost, R M
  - Young, C H
  - Young, Donald
  - Young, Dora E
  - Young, Kimball
  - Young, Mary M
  - Young, Mildred
  - Young, Paul C
  - Young, Paul Thomas
  - Young, Philip
  - Young, William C
  - Yugoslavia, Ambassador of
  - Yuker, Harold E
  - Yuki, Kinichi
  - Zelliot, E A
  - Zigler, Michael J
  - Zunder, Theodore A
  - Zabriskie, Mrs. David
  - Zahl, Paul F M
  - Zalles, Mrs. Rose Saul
  - Zangwill, O L
  - Zarudzki, E F K
  - Zator Company
  - Zelhart, Paul F
  - Zener, Karl
  - Zigler, Michael J
  - Zing Yang Kuo - Articles on Animal Aggression
  - Zinman, R M
  - Zinner, Paul
  - Ziobrowski, Frank
  - Zirkle, Conway
  - Zitek, Edward
  - Zito, Frank A
  - Zubek, John P